

PROFILE

I hold a bachelor's degree in mechanical engineering and a master's degree in Machine Learning for Aeronautics. I am a hardworking, disciplined, and goal-oriented individual. My diverse professional experience across various fields has broadened my vision and strengthened my problem-solving skills, regardless of my position. I thrive in both teamwork and independent tasks, ensuring that my work is precise. With an analytical mindset, I remain focused regardless of workplace dynamics.

CONTACT

PHONE NUMBER: +41 76 626 15 66

EMAIL ADDRESS: gulizar.durmaz@gmail.com

My Website
LinkedIn
Medium
GitHub

LANGUAGES

Turkish- Native English- Advanced (C1) German- Upper-Intermediate(B2) French- Beginner(A1-A2) Polish- Beginner

Gülüzar DURMAZ PIFŃKOWSKI

Year of Birth: 1992 Nationality: Turkish

Sankt Antoni, Fribourg, Switzerland B Permit

EDUCATION

<u>Kocaeli University</u>, Türkiye

02/2020-02/2023

M.Sc. Degree in Aviation Science and Technologies (GPA: 3.72/4.00)

Thesis: Selection of 2D Airfoil During Aircraft Conceptual Design Phase with Machine Learning- UAV, Reference No: 801237

Article: Machine Learning Assisted 2d Airfoil Selection During Aircraft Conceptual Design Phase

Cukurova University, Türkiye

09/2010-06/2018

B.Sc. Degree in Mechanical Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

[Tosyali Holding] [R&D and Artificial Intelligence Engineer], Türkiye 04/2024-08/2024 Project Lead - Enhancing Occupational Safety Detection Using Computer Vision [SAP, Python, Java, Project Management]

[Technical University of Denmark -Space Department] [Earth

Observation Data Scientist-Computer Vision Researcher], Denmark 02/2023-10/2023

Experience in processing Copernicus data (GIS) and developing neural network models with PyTorch/CUDA for large datasets for 4D reconstruction on HPC systems. Proficient in research methodologies.

[Mivul-VBO] [Data Scientist- ML Engineer], Türkiye 03/2022-07/2022

Completed Data Science & Machine Learning Bootcamp, gaining skills in Python, CRM Analytics, AB Testing, Machine Learning, and Neural Networks.

Certificate

[Assemcorp] [Service Contract | Sales Engineer], Türkiye 10/2019-02/2023

SMD Line machines, <u>Comet Yxlon</u> XRay-CT machines, <u>ASM DEK</u> Solder Paste Printers, <u>HaTech</u> laser markers, <u>Nordson</u> Asymtek Conformal Coating machines, Siplace Pro Software

[Yenasoft] [Esprit-CAM Software Support Specialist], Türkiye 01/2019-08/2019

Esprit-CAM (Computer Aided Manufacturing, CNC), SolidWorks (CAD)

SKILLS

